<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>Home - work</title>
    <subtitle>My working blog. Have fun!</subtitle>
    <link href="https://innocentzero.github.io/blog/tags/work/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
    <link href="https://innocentzero.github.io/blog"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2023-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://innocentzero.github.io/blog/tags/work/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Philosophy behind these notes</title>
        <published>2023-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <author>
          <name>Unknown</name>
        </author>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://innocentzero.github.io/blog/about/philosophy/" type="text/html"/>
        <id>https://innocentzero.github.io/blog/about/philosophy/</id>
        
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I believe &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;notes.andymatuschak.org&#x2F;About_these_notes?stackedNotes=z21cgR9K3UcQ5a7yPsj2RUim3oM2TzdBByZu&quot;&gt;Andy Matuschak&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; summarizes the philosophy best in his notes. Often times while working on projects we believe to only make the final view public and hiding the entire intermediate process behind the curtains. This urge for perfection can be seen everywhere courtesy social media and in a broader sense, consumer marketing. &lt;em&gt;You must be perfect to be happy&lt;&#x2F;em&gt;. Often times this ends up removing the joy of learning and working on something.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can also be seen in programmers who create projects. They would try to micro optimise their code, and push to the repo only when they are satisfied with what they have in front of them, which is arguably very rare. On the other hand, opponents of the previous philosophy say that you should &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;sethrobertson.github.io&#x2F;GitBestPractices&#x2F;&quot;&gt;commit often&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. I believe in the latter.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me this philosophy is an attempt to show the world (or in a limited sense, whoever comes across this blog) that the process of ironing out the creases and the wrinkles is more often than not the more fun part in any process. In that regard, if you have nay suggestion regarding this website, feel free to drop them &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;InnocentZero&#x2F;innocentzero.github.io&#x2F;discussions&#x2F;1&quot;&gt;here&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. Your comments and suggestions are always welcome!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
